♪ Your heart has called me♪
♪ Closer to you♪
♪ I will be♪
♪ All that you need♪
♪ Just trust...♪
Baby? Lottie?
We're almost there, okay?
Might want to wake up.
♪ Baby, I believe.♪
- Hi, morning.
- Hey, good morning.
- Can I see your license?
- Uh, yes.
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
All right, I'm-a need
to see your bag.
Oh. Okay.
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
All right now.
- Let me see that bag, too.
- You want this bag?
- Yeah, the backpack. Mm-hmm.
- Oh.
Here.
All right. Thank you.
Is this really necessary?
She's just a child.
You'd be surprised
who's snuck guns in here.
- Here we go.
- Thank you.
You got that. Watch yourself.
Have a good day.
You'll need these at all times.
Hold on to that.
- Okay. Thank you.
- Straight up there.
You got it.
Have a good one, now.
Hello, y'all, and welcome
to Kirkwood Chocolate's
one and only Chocolateland.
A studio for the culture
and what...?
By the culture.
- By the culture, that's right.
- Yes, Lord!
Over here we have
Mr. Chocolate's
state-of-the-art film stages.
- What's that over there?
- Uh,
those are Mr. Chocolate's
old stages and studios.
He's converted them
into a personal office.
Mr. Chocolate
is very... private.
So, no one's allowed in
or out.
All right, moving on.
Hi. We're here for filming.
- Hi. Nice to meet you.
- Oh.
- Yes.
- Um, you can just
sign your name.
- Oh, okay.
- You can sign in over there,
and I'll come and bring you
to hair and makeup
when they're ready for you.
If you need anything,
- please ask, okay?
- Thank you.
FIRST P.A.:
No problem.
Okay, ready?
Good.
Take a break, we'll do it again.
Yo, man, don't come at me
with that bullshit.
You know I had to take Chrissy
to set today.
I'm hungry.
Uh-uh, uh-oh.
Oh. Okay, okay.
If that nigga ain't got
my bands, he dead anyway.
I don't think I brought
any snacks. They're in the car.
Nigga, hold that nigga there.
We'll just grab
something after, okay?
Oh, okay. Okay. Nigga,
hold that nigga's ass there.
Hold him there.
Hold that nigga there!
I told you,
put that nigga in the trunk
if you have to.
Hold that nigga there.
- That's a really nice goldfish.
- Thanks.
Shut up, shut up,
shut up, shut up.
Hey, uh, excuse me.
Yo, I'm sorry
for being loud or whatever.
Oh, it's okay.
Um... what's your name?
Denise.
Nice to meet you, Denise.
Yeah.
FIRST P.A.:
Vanessa.
Oh, we're ready for you.
Uh... Denise,
they're ready for you.
Uh, let's pack up.
- Is this your first time here?
- Oh, yeah.
It's great, isn't it?
Yeah, it's fun.
That's the one you saw
with Grandma.
Baby, you want my phone?
You can have it.
I'm okay.
- Mm, she is so sweet.
- Aw.
I can't tell you
how many kids come through
with a diva attitude.
Thank you.
Honestly,
it's your first time on set.
Both of us, actually.
- Really?
- Mm-hmm.
Are you
a Kirkwood Chocolate fan?
Uh... I haven't really
watched his stuff
in a while, so...
Yeah. I hate it, personally.
Oh.
- No offense.
- No.
No, truly, none taken.
Yeah, honestly, I don't know,
it was just, like,
- a quick way to make
some good money, and...
- Yeah.
And we're supporting Black
art, so I thought that was good,
and... my friend, actually,
told me to audition. It made me
feel kind of independent.
- Mm-hmm.
- So, I thought I'd just
sort of follow that.
Yeah. Yeah, I mean,
- I'm doing this
to get my bread up.
- Mm-hmm.
- And it's an experience,
you know?
- Exactly.
- We deserve that.
- Yeah.
And then, I was also, like,
I don't really care,
so I could just have fun,
and then my daughter could see
me do something I wanted to do.
- Yo, air should be working now.
- Oh, good.
Take a second and look
at the hot water.... Oh, uh...
My bad, I didn't mean
to interrupt you guys.
- Oh, no, you're good.
- It's okay.
- Hi, I'm Shamik.
Hi. Vanessa.
I ain't seen you before.
What show you work on?
Uh, I'm just a day player today.
- Oh, really?
- Mm-hmm.
- Well,
it's nice to meet you.
- You, too.
- I'll see you around. All right.
- All right.
Well, okay, Miss Vanessa.
- I see you.
- Copy. Phaedra.
We're gonna need her
in 40 minutes.
Oh, okay.
Girl, we just... in here
talking. Okay, I'm just gonna...
You don't need him.
Sandra, he is not worth it.
But he's my husband.
If I don't stand with him,
who else will?
What the hell is going on here?
Didn't I tell you
you couldn't have any friends?
Charles, I love you,
but a woman has needs
and boundaries.
You represent me
when you walk out of this house.
I don't care what your little
thot friends over there think.
MALE VOICE [over intercom]:
Dramond.
Grab her by the shoulders.
- Who is that?
- Mr. Chocolate.
MR. CHOCOLATE [over intercom]:
Mikey, please mess up her hair.
More, Mikey.
Thank you. Continue.
I'll be damned
if you embarrass me like that
ever again.
Both of you, out.
Charles, we're here...
- Now.
- Shut up.
Baby. You have to be quiet...
MR. CHOCOLATE:
Who said that?
Uh, I'm sorry.
That was my daughter. Um...
Baby, you have to be quiet
when they're filming, okay?
So they can record it.
Okay, mama?
MR. CHOCOLATE:
May I see her?
Uh, I'm sorry, my daughter?
MR. CHOCOLATE:
Yes.
Uh, s-sure.
Where are you?
MR. CHOCOLATE:
I'm everywhere, like God.
I'm Mr. Chocolate.
Why did you
tell that mean man to shut up?
He was being mean.
I like her.
Put her in the scene.
Mikey, place her on the stairs.
Oh, oh, I'm sorry,
she-she doesn't act.
Everyone acts, Miss Vanessa.
What is your name, young lady?
Lottie.
Can you tell the mean man
to shut up
exactly the way you did
the first time?
Okay.
- Wonderful. Dramond...
- Are you gonna be okay?
...take it from,
"I'll be damned."
I'll be damned
if you embarrass me
like that ever again.
Both of you, out.
Charles, we're here supporting...
- Now.
- Shut up.
MR. CHOCOLATE:
Amazing. Cut. Moving on.
Oh, but, Mr. Chocolate, um,
that was just
the blocking rehearsal,
and Lottie's not in
any of the earlier scenes.
We'll fix it in post.
But, sir,
the post department
has been begging us
to fix it in "pre."
Understood, sir.
Call Marcie in costumes. We're
gonna need children's clothes.
I'm sorry,
what-what-what's happening?
Oh, Mr. Chocolate
just needs Lottie
in the next scene.
How long's that gonna take?
With the way that
Mr. Chocolate shoots,
you'll both still probably
be done by lunch,
but we just need
to get her fitted.
Come with me, please.
Can I wear this?
It's up to your mother, darling,
but Mr. Chocolate says
whatever you want.
- This okay?
- Yeah,
that's fine.
You okay, love?
You nervous for her?
Yeah. I guess
I'm kind of nervous.
Well, she seems to be
very excited.
She'll do fine.
Yeah, but I guess, like,
putting children
on screen, you know,
I don't know if she really
understands the bigger picture
of what we're doing,
you know what I mean?
What have you seen
of Mr. Chocolate's?
Not a lot. Um...
I saw that one movie
where the woman marries...
an angel.
Oh, yeah. Do Not Be Afraid.
Yes, yes.
I, um, didn't love that one.
You a Christian?
I'm spiritual.
It's okay.
None of us are perfect.
The only reason I ask
is because it always reminds me
of this verse, "Whoever
"doesn't receive the
Kingdom of God like a child,
won't enter it."
And I always thought
that meant whoever's not open
to the joys of a child--
like their own child--
is not really open
to true happiness.
Mom. Mom.
Looks cool, huh?
Wow.
It looks very cool.
Can I make a video?
I look like Doja Cat.
Listen, Doja.
If you ever feel uncomfortable,
and you want to leave,
you just give me
the "thumbs down" sign,
and we go right then and there.
We don't even have to talk
to anybody, okay?
Okay.
Want to shake on it?
We're ready for Lottie on set.
All right, baby.
Come on, let's go.
I don't like that man, Mama.
I don't like how he treats you.
I know, baby,
but he's all I got.
Your mama's crazy.
If my mama's crazy,
what's your mama?
You better tell her.
MR. CHOCOLATE [over intercom]:
Cut.
Moving on. That was perfect.
Lottie.
Lottie?
She's good.
Thank you.
Honestly, we need
to stick together.
Mr. Chocolate
likes your daughter,
probably writing a kids show
for her right now.
Maybe my daughter
could be the best friend
who's good at computers.
Nah.
She's, uh,
just acting for today.
Honestly, she's not even
really that into acting.
I don't know.
She seems pretty happy.
Yeah, no. She's...
she's not ready.
But your daughter
should have the show.
Oh, I know.
She's not the right "type."
Like I said, we really need
to stick together.
How was that, Mommy?
That was great.
That was great. Yes.
Excuse me, s-- Where's Lottie?
They moved to the next scene.
- Next scene?
- Mm-hmm.
How many more scenes is she in?
Well, she's in...
uh...
14 more scenes,
and it looks like they made her
number three on the call sheet. Congratulations.
Oh, no, no, no.
I think I need
to speak to somebody in charge.
Is Mr. Chocolate around?
No.
He never leaves his office.
I've actually never seen
Mr. Chocolate.
I just know
he's always watching me.
Guy's a genius.
That's fine.
Um, where is Lottie headed?
Tommy Lister Memorial Stage.
- Okay, could you take me there?
- I...
I'll take you, if you want.
So, where you from?
I'm from here. You?
Oh, I'm from New Orleans.
Don't worry, I still like you, though.
Think it's cool seeing a mother
and daughter working together.
How long y'all been acting?
Uh, we actually
don't really act.
A friend of mine put me on,
and I was told
maybe it'd be
a good experience for me.
Oh, well, you guys are great.
How'd you end up
in maintenance here?
I got incarcerated
when I was young.
Two years and...
wasn't a lot of opportunity
when I got out.
Mr. Chocolate,
he had this program.
Just thought
I'd build up my résumé
and work on coding at night.
- Coding?
- Yeah, I got this
crypto mining farm.
It's in my closet.
I've been playing
with solar batteries, too.
Do you even know what that is?
Or am I just, like...
am I mansplaining?
You're doing a little bit
of both, but it's cute enough.
Look, uh, there it is.
- Okay.
- Look, I got to run, but...
you ever got a problem
with your fridge or your phone,
or you just want
to get coffee...
you should hit me.
- Thank you.
- Oh, yeah, for sure.
You white piece of shit.
I hope you get shot
in the theatre.
MR. CHOCOLATE [over intercom]:
And cut. Flip the set.
SECOND P.A.:
Uh, Mr. Chocolate,
that was a blocking.
We weren't filming.
MR. CHOCOLATE:
We'll fix it in post.
Flip the set.
Um, excuse me, Miss? Sorry.
Have you seen my daughter?
She's a little girl with
cornrows? They said she would be
- on this set.
- Uh, I think
they're on the
John Witherspoon Stage now.
Okay, I'm sorry.
This is unacceptable.
Who is with my daughter?
I'm sorry.
I'm directing two pilots
and starring in another.
I just bring people
where he tells me.
Mr. Chocolate is the only person
who actually knows
what's going on.
You need to bring me
to my daughter right now.
- Right now. Yes?
- Okay.
- Thank you.
- Yeah, yeah.
You realize you can't just
take somebody's child
without their permission?
That that's kidnapping?
Ma'am, I'm sorry this happened,
but you won't even remember this
when she wins that BET Award.
Award? This script has a woman
eating a crack sandwich.
Yeah.
- Man, that's good.
- Mr. Chocolate is a wild boy.
What was I even thinking?
I can't believe
I let her do this.
I wouldn't even
let her watch this.
SECOND P.A.:
Well, my kids love it.
It's funny.
Me and my grandma
watch his HIV drama,
Love After Diagnosis,
sometimes after church.
I love his rap musical
about the Black law professor
that kills
all her white students.
Yeah.
- That show is lit.
- Yeah, but it's not good.
I don't know. He won,
like, 30 NAACP Awards
- and a bunch of BET ones.
- Mm-hmm. Yeah.
Yeah, so Black awards.
So, only the white ones
matter to you?
You know what I mean.
Say what you want
about Mr. Chocolate,
- but he's done a lot
for the community.
- SECOND P.A.: Yep.
I'm rooting
for everybody Black.
Mm.
Even O.J.?
- Even O.J.
Look, I tried.
Lord knows I tried.
And I don't know
what they said about me,
I don't, I don't know
what you heard, okay?
But sometimes you don't get
the answers you're looking for.
Go ahead and ask me something.
Why am I here, Mama?
None of us asked to be here.
You just go through life
and hope for the best.
But why am I here with you?
Why... didn't you protect me?
Isn't that what mothers
are supposed to do?
This crack sandwich
good as hell.
MR. CHOCOLATE [over intercom]:
Amazing. Moving on.
Lottie? Lottie?
Where is she?
Um...
I'm sorry, ma'am.
I don't know where she is.
But I'm sure she's safe.
Mr. Chocolate
is always watching, and...
he has plans for her.
What the fuck are you saying?
Is this a fucking cult?
Um, e-excuse me, s-security?
I'm sorry, um...
- Mm-hmm?
- I can't find my daughter.
Okay, but I can't actually
help you, though.
You're security.
Uh, technically, but
I'm also just an intern, too.
Here's your coffee.
Thanks.
Give me back my daughter.
MR. CHOCOLATE:
No.
Hell no.
Hey. Hey, love.
You okay?
♪ Uh♪
♪ I do as I want,
I do as I like♪
♪ I no watch face, I no fear♪
♪ Nobody, nobody...♪
Hey!
Kirkwood has my daughter.
I need to see her.
- This is a private
residence, ma'am.
- Okay, this is ridiculous.
He has my daughter,
and I'm gonna get in there.
Ma'am, we're gonna call
the police.
You know what? Call the police.
I want them here.
- Give me my daughter.
- It's okay, it's okay.
- No. No, no, no.
- Tell me what's happening.
- Kirkwood has my daughter,
and nobody's fucking
helping me find her!
- And I don't know what to do
'cause nobody's helping me.
- It's okay. Shh...
- I just need...
- It's okay, it's okay.
- Okay. Okay, okay. Okay.
- I got you. Don't you worry.
Okay.
Let her in.
She has no clearance, ma'am.
This is Mr. Chocolate's
- personal space.
- Mm. Okay.
Oh, shit.
Ma'am, these are fake M16s
from the film War of God.
Please don't shoot me.
Go in, baby.
♪ Point and kill♪
♪ You can't stop me, oh...♪
♪ You can't stop me,
point and kill.♪
Okay.
:
Mr. Chocolate?
Oh, hello.
I was just writing
on my "Key-iano."
Scripts are like music to me.
Steve Jobs made that for me.
I think of him
every time I write.
Would you like a grit?
Where's my daughter?
She's right there.
On the Mario Van Peebles Stage.
By the time you get there,
she'll have moved on
to the next scene...
...and the next stage.
Where is the next stage?
I don't know.
This whole operation
runs on its own.
I do not understand its...
wants and needs,
nor do I control them.
Chocolateland is my child.
I protect her,
guide her,
but she is not my own.
Have her say,
"But I'm pregnant."
FIRST P.A. [over intercom]:
But this is a kids' show,
Mr. Chocolate.
Thank you.
I'm calling the police.
I own the police.
And most of College Park.
You can't just
take somebody's...
I can do whatever I want!
You break into my cube,
shoot my guard, and then
tell me how to raise my child?!
This is an open carry state,
Ms. Vanessa.
You know, someone as you...
I'm fine.
Grits don't work on me.
I've developed a tolerance
over the years.
Oh, my God.
You're a con man.
You just make unrelatable
shit that takes advantage
of the people
- you say you're trying to help.
- Mr. Chocolate?
Oh, my God. Baby? Baby!
- It's an honor, sir.
- Are you okay?
- Oh, so...
- Yeah, it was fun.
- Everyone said that I was funny.
- Really? Are you okay?
- Yeah.
- You okay?
Uh, Ms. Keifer,
- could you please sign
this time sheet?
- Absolutely not.
"Unrelatable shit," you say.
You know, I've been
watching you, Ms. Keifer.
You're a single mother who can't
afford to feed your daughter.
Phaedra is your
"hip girlfriend."
You have a
"formally incarcerated,
light-skinned love interest,"
a "Christian,
gun-toting grandmother,"
and let me guess,
you have a dark-skinned
baby daddy?
He's brown-skinned.
And you threw grits at me.
Unprovoked.
Face it, Vanessa,
you're
a Kirkwood Chocolate woman.
Well, maybe I am, but that
doesn't make you an artist.
It doesn't.
It makes me a philanthropist.
And I'd like
to make Lottie an offer.
Six seasons
of a children's show.
That would make her
financially stable
until she was 20.
What do you say?
Well, I'm not like one
of those mothers downstairs
that's gonna make
their daughter do something
they don't want to do.
I want to do it.
I want to be
on Mr. Chocolate's show.
:
No.
- No! No!
- Lottie.
- Lottie. Please, Lottie.
- She wants to stay.
- No!
- She doesn't.
She can't be not-18 forever.
Lottie. Please, Lottie.
- We have to...
- I shall have her.
She'll be
"Spurned Woman Number Eight"
when I'm done with her!
Lottie, please.
I've lost a lot of blood,
Mikey. Could you please, um...
- Could you call an ambulance?
- Oh, sir. Of course. Um...
Lottie. Come here.
Baby, I want to talk
about what happened, okay?
No.
I know you were having a lot
of fun today.
And...
I'm really sorry
that it ended how it ended, hmm?
But you represent something.
And I know it isn't fair, but
what you do-- it matters a lot.
And... I just really want you
to be old enough
to decide what you want
to represent, okay?
'Cause I...
I can't always protect you.
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
It shouldn't have happened
like that.
Oh. I love you, baby.
You, too.
I'm always gonna be here
for you, okay?
Okay.
I'm gonna make mac and cheese.
♪ 3:00 on the dot♪
♪ He pull up on my block♪
♪ We goin' to the mall♪
♪ I'm getting' Nike Shox♪
♪ No, I'm not Baroque but
he treats me like he's Bach♪
♪ I take a little off the top♪
♪ He my dog, Iggy Pop♪
♪ Shopping bag, it's Goyard♪
♪ You lookin' mad, I go hard♪
♪ I'm on a yacht, no lifeguard♪
♪ You not my man,
you a blowhard♪
♪ He givin' me the keys
to the brand-new Benz♪
♪ We chillin' waterfront
but we're not holding hands♪
♪ Wishy washy♪
♪ Not my boyfriend but
I let you take me shopping♪
♪ Buy me what I want,
I want it all♪
♪ Wishy washy♪
♪ I like the attention
but don't get too comfy♪
♪ Wishy washy♪
♪ Wish, wishy♪
♪ Wish, wishy washy♪
♪ Wishy washy♪
♪ Wish, wishy washy.♪
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH access.wgbh.org